Guide to the Ann Brewer Knox papers, 1935-2011 MS2305
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Poetry and short fiction, 1977-2011; Series 1
  - Book manuscripts, 1986-2011; Series 1 Subseries 2
    - Caught moment, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Caught moment / Rona, circa 2010; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Chekhov paper copy, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Clean copy stories already published, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Dark edge ms, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Early ms, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Eve, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Eve, circa 2010; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Eve, 2006 March; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Eve cb, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Eve cb, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Eve learns the word want, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Eve learns the word want ms, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Eve ms, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Eve ms, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Eve ms, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Eve ms, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Fiction ms, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Fiction ms, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Handful of stories, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Late summer break original ms, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Light from another room, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Light from another room, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Light from another room, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Light from another room, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Light from another room, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Light from another room, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Light from another room, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Light from another room, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Light from another room, circa 2008; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Light from another room, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Light from another room, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Light from another room, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Light from another room, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Light from another room, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Light from another room original, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Light from another room ms, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Light from another room ms, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Light ms, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Means of address old ms incomplete, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Miles traveled cb, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Moving on ms, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Moving on ms, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Moving on ms, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Moving on s.s. original, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Moving on s.s. ms, circa 2001; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder data_value_missing_5de68d8e85d5faf4e656473d4641ba00)
    - Moving on s. story ms, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Moving on short stories, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Moving on short stories, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Reading the Tao at 80, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Reading the Tao at 80, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Reading the Tao at 80 backup, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Tao, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Tao, circa 2008; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Tao ms comments, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Tao ms crits, 2006; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Rituals for a journey, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Rituals for a journey, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Rituals for a journey ms, 1993 April; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Rona, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Short stories copies, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Short takes of eve, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Short takes of eve, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Short takes of eve, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Short takes of eve, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Songs for a crone chapbook, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Staying is nowhere, 1995 March 3; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Staying is nowhere ms, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Stonecrop ms, 1986 August 2; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Stonecrop ms, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Stonecrop ms, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Stonecrop ms, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - To reckon chpbk, 1999 November; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - To reckon distance, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - To reckon distance, circa 1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - To reckon distance, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - To reckon distance ms, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - To reckon distance ms, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - To reckon distance ms, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - To reckon distance ms, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - To reckon new ms poetry, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Publications, 1977-2011; Series 1 Subseries 3
    Arranged alphabetically by folder/publication title.
    This subseries contains published journals, articles, chapbooks, and books, which contain poems by Ann B. Knox. Including among the publications are copies of Stonecrop, Staying in Nowhere, Breathing-In, Late Summer Break, Reading the Tao at Eight, The Dark Edge, The journals and reviews include Alaska Quarterly Review, Atlanta Review, Baltimore Review, Blueline, Comstock Review, Cumberland Poetry Review, Green Mountains Review, MacGuffin, Nimrod, Plum Review, Poerty, Poets On, Potomac Review, and WordWrights. Copies of Antietam Review include interview of poets written by Knox. The material dates from 1977 to 2011.
    - Alaska quarterly review, 1991; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - American poets and poetry, 1998 November-December; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Antietam review, 1984-1989; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Antietam review, 1990-1994; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Antietam review, 1996-2001; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Apalachee quarterly, 1995-1996; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Ascent, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Atlanta review, 1996, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Baltimore review, 1997 summer; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Berkeley poetry review, 1986 fall; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Blue guitar, undated; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Blue unicorn, 2008 October; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Blueline, 1987, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Breathing in, 2011; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Cabin fever: poets at joaquin miller's cabin, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Cedar Rock, 1981 fall, 1982 winter; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Circus maximus, 1977 November; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Confrontation no. 107, 2010 summer; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Cumberland poetry review, 1986 spring, 1992 fall; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Dark edge, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Each in her own way: women writing on the menopause, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Embers: the poetry of woman, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Free lunch no. 40 and 41, 2008 autumn, 2009 autumn; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Free state: a harvest of maryland poets, 1989; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Fresh water: poems from the rivers, lakes, and streams, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Gold dust: a journal of contemporary poetry, 1987 January; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Green mountain review, 1988, 1996; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Green's magazine, 1981 winter; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Hampden-sydney poetry review, 2001 winter; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Hungry as we are: an anthology of washington area poets, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Implosion issue 3, 1988 April; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Intro 10, 1979; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Joyful noise: friendly creatures 2, 1996; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Juggler's world, 1991 summer; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Laurels: eight women poets, 1998; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Late Summer Break, Undated; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Macguffin, 1985 fall, 1988 fall; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Madog arts magazine, 1981 spring; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Main street rag, 2009 spring; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Maryland poetry review, 1988 spring/summer; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Metropolitain, 1992 summer; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Monocacy valley review, 1986 autumn, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Monocacy valley review, 1989 summer; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - My shameless st. augustine scrapbook, 1998; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Negative capability, 1990; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - New letters: a magazine of fine writing, 1987-1988 winter; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - New york quarterly, 1991; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Night sun issue 18, 1998 fall; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Nimrod (clap hands and sing), 1991; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Ohio poetry review, 1994 fall/winter; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Out of a/maze, 1996; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Out of season, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Over the wall literary review, 1992 winter; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Phoebe: the george mason review, 1985 fall; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Plum review, 1991 spring/summer; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Poems and plays no. 9, 2002 spring/summer; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Poet lore, 1987-1988 winter, 1989 fall; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Poetry, 1990 October, 1992 February, 1994 October; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Poetry bone issue 3, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Poets on: giving, 1987 summer; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Poets on: parting, 1993 summer; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Poets on: regret, 1984 summer; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Poets on: touching, 1979 summer; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Potomac appalachian, 1978 December; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Potomac review, 1994 summer, 1996 fall, 1997 winter; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Potomac review, 2005-2006 fall/winter; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Potpourri, 1993 september; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Reading the tao at eighty, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Signatures #11, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Soundings east, 1985 spring/summer; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Sparrow 59, 1992 september; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Splinters and fragments: earth's daughters, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Staying is Nowhere, Undated; Series 1 subseries 3 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Stone canoe no. 4, 2010 spring; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Takoma voice, 1998 November; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Visions international no. 36, 1991; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Warren wilson review, 1990 fall, 1991 summer, 1993 winter; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - World wrights no. 16, 1999 summer; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Wpfw 89.3 fm poetry anthology, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Writer's center carousel, 1987 december; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Interviews - Antietam review, 1987-1997; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Interviews - Antietam review, 1989-1996; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Disks and CDs, circa 1987-2008; Series 1 Subseries 4
    Arranged by disk size in a single oversized box.
    This subseries contains 5 1⁄4-inch floppy disks, 3 1⁄2-inch floppy disks, a few CDs, and one cassette tape. The disks include digital version of manuscripts, poetry drafts, personal files, journal entries, and teaching material by Ann Knox. Most of the disks are labeled but few have dates. The material dates from circa 1987 to circa 2008.
    - Digital records, circa 1987 - circa 2008; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 36)
      This subseries consists of one oversize box of 5 1⁄4-inch floppy disks, 3 1⁄2-inch floppy disks, a few cds, and one cassette tape. Most of the disks are labeled but few have dates. The disks include digital version of manuscripts, poetry drafts, personal files, journal entries, and teaching material.
- Personal and professional papers, circa 1935 to 2011; 1977-2011; Series 2
  This series contains personal journals, childhood poems, correspondence, publication material, public relations material, teaching material, clippings, poetry by other authors, and papers related to writing groups and workshops. This material documents the personal and professional writing and teaching career of Ann B. Knox, excluding most of her poetry and short story writings. The bulk of the material dates from 1977 to 2011, when Knox was active in this work. Some earlier material dates from her childhood, including adolescent poems, dating from circa 1935 to 1976.
  Organized into four subseries: Journals; Biographical and publishing material; Correspondence; and Writing groups, workshops, and teaching material
  - Journals, 1976-2011; Series 2 Subseries 1
    Arranged chronologically by year. Knox wrote in multiple journals at the same time, so the journals cover overlapping dates.
    This series contains journals written by of Ann B. Knox. The journal entries relate to her writing, family, daily activities, dreams, and other topics. The material dates from 1976-2011.
    - Journals, 1976 May 28 - 1976 October 30; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Journals, 1976 October 16 - 1977 August 7; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Journals, 1977 April - 1977 July; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Journals, 1978 January 1 - 1978 July 18; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Journals, 1978 July - 1978 September 3; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Journals, 1978 September 4 - 1978 October 29; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Journals, 1978 April 9 - 1979 January 7; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Journals, 1979 January 7 - 1979 April 22; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Journals, 1979 April 27 - 1979 October 8; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Journals, 1979 September 5 - 1985 October 28; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Journals, 1979 October 28 - 1980 April 22; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Journals, 1980 April 23 - 1980 November 19; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Journals, 1980 November 20 - 1981 March 12; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Journals, 1981 March 12 - 1981 August 8; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Journals, 1981 August 13 - 1981 November 3; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Journals, 1981 November 8 - 1982 January 4; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Journals, 1982 January 9 - 1982 June 10; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Journals, 1982 June 12 - 1982 November 1; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Journals, 1982 November 2 - 1983 April 20; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Journals, 1983 April 22 - 1983 August 25; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Journals, 1983 August 29 - 1984 January 20; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Journals, 1984 January 20 - 1984 April 6; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Journals, 1984 April 10 - 1984 July 21; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Journals, 1984 July 21 - 1984 December 18; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Journals, 1984 December 22 - 1985 June 2; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Journals, 1985 June 3 - 1985 November 18; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Journals, 1985 November 19 - 1986 March 4; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Journals, 1986 March 7 - 1986 September 16; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Journals, 1986 August 16 - 1987 February 4; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Journals, 1987 January 1 - 1987 June 5; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Journals, 1987 February 7 - 1987 November 22; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Journals, 1987 July 23 - 1988 March 26; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Journals, 1987 December 5 - 1988 September 5; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Journals, 1988 March 27 - 1988 September 1; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Journals, 1988 Septmeber 2 - 1989 January 12; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Journals, 1988 December 24 - 1989 April 27; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Journals, 1989 April 24 - 1989 October 21; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Journals, 1989 August 5 - 1990 March 5; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Journals, 1989 October 26 - 1990 July 24; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Journals, 1990 March 12 - 1990 September 8; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Journals, 1990 July 31 - 1990 December 8; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Journals, 1990 December 8 - 1991 June 16; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Journals, 1991 February 18 - 1991 November 12; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Journals, 1991 June 17 - 1991 September 24; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Journals, 1991 May 31 - 1992 March 18; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Journals, 1991 November 13 - 1992 May 10; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Journals, 1992 February 24 - 1992 September 1; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Journals, 1992 May 11 - 1992 December 24; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Journals, 1992 Septmeber 18 - 1993 June 10; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Journals, 1992 Decmeber 26 - 1993 May 8; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Alaska journal hard copy, 1993 June 24 - 1993 August 15; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Alaska journal, 1993 Julu 4 - 1993 August 7; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Alaska journal, 1993 August 7 - 1993 August 15; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Journals, 1993 May 9 - 1993 October 17; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Journals, 1993 June 16 - 1994 January 24; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Journals, 1994 January 13 - 1994 June 4; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Journals, 1994 April 13 - 1994 October 15; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Journals, 1994 June 9 - 1995 January 23; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Journals, 1994 November 12 - 1995 April 8; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Journals, 1995 March 30 - 1995 Septmeber 11; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Journals, 1995 August 20 - 1996 February 22; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Journals, 1995 December 3 - 1996 July 13; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Journals, 1996 March 10 - 1996 October 7; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Journals, 1996 September 24 - 1997 March 10; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Journals, 1997 February 6 - 1997 December 31; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Journals, 1997 Julu 16 - 1997 December 4; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Journals, 1997 December 5 - 1998 June 3; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Journals, 1998 March 29 - 1998 November 26; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Journals, 1998 August 26 - 1999 April 1; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Journals, 1999 March 4 - 1999 November 21; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Journals, 1999 April 13 - 2000 March 14; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Journals, 2000 March 23 - 2001 January 8; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Journals, 2000 July 4 - 2001 May 2; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Journals, 2001 March 9 - 2001 November 10; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Journals, 2001 April 15 - 2002 April 3; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Journals, 2001 November 11 - 2002 November 28; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Journals, 2002 April 4 - 2003 February 5; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Journals, 2002 November 29 - 2003 March 27; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Journals, 2003 March 28 - 2003 October 13; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Journals, 2003 October 8 - 2004 March 14; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Journals, 2004 January 29 - 2004 November 19; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Journals, 2004 September 19 - 2005 May 9; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Journals, 2004 November 30 - 2006 January 22; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Journals, 2005 June 26 - 2006 June 11; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Journals, 2006 March 16 - 2007 January 10; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Journals, 2006 October 15 - 2007 June 7; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Journals, 2007 January 6 - 2007 November 10; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Journals, 2007 June 12 - 2008 April 15; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Journals, 2008 February 17 - 2008 October 18; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Journals, 2008 May 1 - 2009 February 20; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Journals, 2009 January 29 - 2009 November 4; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 1)